# Xie Fen (Joy)

fenx@uw.edu 206.201.4312 4428 Eastern Ave N, Seattle, WA

http://joyoverseas.com/

### Skills

#### **Design Methods**

Storyboards Personas and Scenarios Wireframe Prototyping Usability Testing

#### **Design Tools**

Illustrator Photoshop InDesign

#### **Programming**

HTML/CSS/Javascript Python Java Cobol, DB2

#### **Data Analysis**

R, Rstudio Machine Learning (Octave)

### Summary

Over 4 years industry experience with wide ranging job roles and diverse cultural backgrounds. Passionate in design technology and currently pursuing a master's degree in Human Computer Interaction and Design at University of Washington. Seeking for UI/UX designer position starting from fall 2015.

### Work Experience

#### **Product Manager** | 03/2013-11/2013

Opera Software ASA, Beijing, China

Coordinated 15+ people team and managed the new release of Opera Mini Chinese version for millions of monthly active users.

Led 10 people team and launched Sphinx, a browser-based game engine in 3 months.

#### **QA Engineer** | 06/2011-03/2013

Opera Software ASA, Beijing, China

Developed 5+ Opera speed dial extensions, one of which reached 200,000 downloads. Led the outsourcing project of developing 10+ apps for Opera TV Store. Presented Opera products in exhibitions and gave speeches in developer conferences. Conducted quality assurance work on Opera Desktop, Mobile and TV Store, including automated testing.

#### **Software Engineer** | 08/2007-08/2008

Infosys Technologies Limited, Shanghai, China

Developed banking backend services under Mainframe system using Cobol and DB2. Collected and analysed customer requirements onsite.

## Internship

#### Sales Assistant | 03/2010-09/2010

Ilmed Ventilazione Industriale, Torino, Italy

Developed and maintained customer relationship, provided after sales support. Coordinated order processing between China and Italy offices, shortened delivery by improving process.

#### **Software Intern** | 09/2006-04/2007

Infosys Technologies Limited, Mysore, India

Got A in all the courses of 3 months' high-demanding Mainframe training. Led an 8 people team to achieve an evaluation of ranking A in the final project.

### Education

**Master of Human Computer Interaction and Design** | 09/2014- 08/2015 *University of Washington, U.S.* 

Master of Computer Engineering, GPA 102/110 | 09/2008-12/2010 Politecnico di Torino, Italy

**B.S in Software Engineering, GPA 87.8/100** | 09/2003-07/2007

Huazhong University of Science and Technology, China